[Adalo 2.0 is now available! Learn how you can build custom responsive apps without code!](https://www.adalo.com/adalo-2-0)

Product

Solutions

Learn

Support

Support

Privacy Policy
==============

**Apto Labs, Inc. Privacy Policy**  
Last updated: May 3rd, 2019.  
‍  
Apto Labs, Inc. (“Company,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) values the privacy of individuals who use our website, mobile application (the “App”), and related services (collectively, the “Service”). This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes the information that we gather from visitors, users, and others who access or use the Service (“Users,” “you,” or “your”), how we use and disclose such information, and the steps we take to protect such information. By using the Service, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy.  
‍  
This Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Aptos Labs, Inc. Terms of Use. Capitalized terms used but not defined in this Policy have the meaning given to them in the Terms of Use.  
‍  
**1\. Information We Collect**  
_Personal information you disclose to us  
_‍While using the Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, other contact and demographic information, password and security information, and payment information. All payment information is stored by our payment processor and you should review their privacy policies and contact them directly with any questions. You may provide us with Personal Information when you register for an Account, use the Service, make a purchase on the Service, contact customer support, or otherwise communicate with us. All Personal Information that you provide to us must be true, complete and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.  
  
_Information automatically collected_  
‍We collect information about how you access and interact with the Service, such as device type, IP address, operating system, browser type, referring URLs, activity on our website, device ID, access dates and times, location information, and other system activity. We may collect certain information by automated means using technologies such as cookies, web beacons, pixels, browser analysis tools, server logs, and mobile identifiers. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes. For example, we may use information we collect to better understand website traffic patterns and to optimize our users’ experience.  
_  
Information collected from the App  
‍_If you use our App, we may request access or permission to and track location-based information from your mobile device, either continuously or while you are using the App, to provide location-based services. We may also request access or permission to certain features from your mobile device, including your mobile device’s camera, storage, photos, and other features. Additionally, we may request to send you push notifications regarding your Account or the App. If you wish to change our access or permissions or opt-out from receiving push-notifications, you may turn such features off in your device’s settings.      
  
**2\. How We Use Your Information**  
_Provide, maintain, and improve the Service  
‍_We may use your information to:  
\- facilitate the creation and securing of your Account  
\- provide customer service  
\- send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages  
\- detect and prevent fraud  
\- operate, protect, and optimize the Service and your experience, such as by performing analytics and conducting research troubleshoot and protect against errors  
\- personalize and improve the Service monitor and analyze usage and trends and otherwise measure the effectiveness of the Service  
develop new features  
‍  
_Sharing your information  
‍_If you use our Service, you are authorizing us to share information:  
\- that you direct us to disclose to others  
\-with our third-party business partners, vendors, and consultants who perform services on our behalf or who help us provide our Services, such as accounting, managerial, technical, marketing, or analytic services  
\- if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with local, state, or federal laws, or to respond to a court order, judicial or other governmental subpoena or warrant, or in the event of bankruptcy proceedings  
\- if we believe in good faith that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our users, our employees, copyright owners, third parties, or the public, including without limitation to protect us or our users from fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate, or unlawful use of our Service  
\- to enforce or apply this Policy, our Terms of Use, or our other policies or agreements  
\- in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, or in any other situation where information may be disclosed or transferred as one of our business assets of  
  
Nothing herein restricts the sharing of aggregated or anonymized information, which may be shared with third parties without your consent. This Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate or de-identified information.  
_  
Links to third-party sites and services  
‍_The Service may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content provided to or contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, this Policy does not apply to those third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on our Service, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. Please read those rules and policies before proceeding.  
‍  
**3\. How We Protect Your Information**  
We take measures designed to protect your information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. To protect the confidentiality of information maintained in your Account, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Service by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused. We will only retain your Personal Information as long as reasonably required for you to use the Service and/or to provide you with the Service unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (for example, for regulatory purposes).  
‍  
**4\. International Data Transfers**  
Personal Information we collect from you may be stored and processed in any country where we have operations or where we engage service providers. We may transfer your Personal Information to recipients in countries other than the country in which the Personal Information was originally collected, including to the United States, where data protection laws may differ from the laws of the country where you are a resident. By providing us with your data you acknowledge and agree that your Personal Information may be processed for the purposes identified in this Policy. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy.  
‍  
**5\. California Privacy Rights**  
Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents have the right to request and obtain a list of the third parties, if any, to which personal information (as defined by California law) has been disclosed for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately prior calendar year. If you are a California resident and want a copy of this information, please submit a written request to us at the address provided in the Contact section below. In your request, please specify that you are requesting a “Your California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow 30 days for a response.  
‍  
**6\. Children’s Privacy**  
Persons under the age of 13, or any higher minimum age in the jurisdiction where that person resides, are not permitted to create accounts unless their parent has consented in accordance with applicable law. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under the relevant minimum age without parental consent, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible. Parents who believe that their child has submitted personal information to us and would like to have it deleted may contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.adalo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  
‍  
**7\. Opting Out**  
You may “opt out” of receiving marketing or promotional emails from us by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your Account or our ongoing business relations.  
‍  
**8\. Changes and Updates to the Policy**  
We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. Please revisit this page periodically to stay aware of any changes. If we modify this Policy, we will make it available through the Service and indicate the date of the latest revision. Your continued use of the Service after the revised Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood, and agreed to the current version of this Policy.  
‍  
**9\. Contact**  
Please contact us with any questions regarding this Policy at [\[email protected\]](https://www.adalo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or at the address below.  
  
Adalo  
911 Washington Avenue  
Suite 501  
St. Louis, MO 63101  

‍

What App Are You Going to Make Today?
-------------------------------------

👋 Join the Adalo Community

[](https://twitter.com/AdaloHQ)[](https://www.facebook.com/AdaloHQ)[](https://www.linkedin.com/company/adalohq)[](https://angel.co/adalo)[\[email protected\]](https://www.adalo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Stay in the loop on everything Adalo! Subscribe today!

Welcome to the community! Updates coming your way soon.

Oh no! Something went wrong! Please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.adalo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Links & Stuff

Copyright 2024 Adalo, Inc. All rights reserved.

Product

Solutions

Resources

Compare

Company

🍪

By clicking **"Accept"**, you agree to the storing of cookies on your device to enhance site navigation, analyze site usage, and assist in our marketing efforts.
